downera.net 2011-11-23

# waresec | Privacy Policy WareSec - Your Daily Dose of Releases

By using our Web site, you consent to the collection and use of this information by waresec.com. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post the changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. Currently, waresec.com may provide aggregate statistics about our traffic patterns, and related site information to reputable third-party vendors, but these statistics will include no personal identifying information.

waresec.com is committed to protecting your privacy. waresec.com does not sell, trade or rent your personal information to other companies. waresec.com will not collect any personal information about you except when you specifically and knowingly provide such information.

Third Party Advertising  
Shall be updated if/when we have any.

Third Party Cookies  
In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser.

Modification of Privacy Policy  
waresec.com reserves the right, at any time, to modify, alter or update the Privacy Policy and you agree to be bound by such modifications, alterations or updates.

Use of Information  
waresec.com will not reveal any personal information that users provide to us to any third party without their permission. waresec.com uses users’ IP addresses to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our website. We also use it to gather broad demographic information about our users in general. This information does not contain anything that can identify users personally.

Using e-mail addresses provided at forum registration or otherwise, waresec.com may periodically sends out e-mail updates as form of newsletters to our users. Users can indicate that they do not wish to receive e-mail information from waresec.com.

Although waresec.com does not specifically seek to obtain any information from minors, this website is open to all. We urge children to use our website only after they have discussed it with their parents.

waresec.com generates search results automatically from databases and any search may return unexpected or unwanted references. These references may contain offensive, obscene, or illegal material. Because waresec.com merely links to and does not publish content supplied by third parties or which is generally available on the Internet, waresec.com has no editorial control over such information. Please use this site and any material referred on it responsibly.
